Guide to the New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH) Records WAG.029
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: Activities, 1979-1987
  - Subseries A: The Committee to Save OSHA, 1979-1983
    - Occupational Safety & Health Improvement Act of 1980 (S. 2153) Information Sheets and Summaries, Dec 19, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Williams to McKowne, Dec 19, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Labor Department Memorandum on Schweiker-Williams Bill, Jan 2, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Department of Labor Report on Reliability of Workers Compensation Reports for Exemptions, Jan 14, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Analysis of Workers' Compensation and S. 2153 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Congressional Record: Introduction of Schweiker Bill S. 2153, Dec 9, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Mailing List (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Contacts (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Organizational Contact Logs (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Urban Environment Conference Organization List (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Municipal Labor Committee: Letter to Schweiker, Jan 24, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Nelson to Williams, Jan 25, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Williams to Opposition, Jan 25, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Williams to Consumer Commission, Jan 31, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - American Public Health Association to Williams, Jan 31, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Christian Science Monitor Solicitation, Jan 31, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Committee to Save OSHA (Letters for Mailing, Correspondence, Reciepts), Jan - Sep 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Schweiker Letter to Opposition, Feb 4, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - OSHA Information, Schweiker Bill and Summaries, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - COPE Memorandum, Feb 2, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Organizational Contact Logs (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Genetic Screening, Feb 5, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Committee to Save OSHA NYC Labor Support Committee (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - New Sponsors of S. 2153, Feb 5, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Cranston Call for Oversight Hearings, Feb 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, Feb 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Mailing 1, Feb 15, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Urban Environment Conference Mailing, Feb 15, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Fund Raising Letters, Jan - Apr 1980 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Schweiker to Martello, Feb 20, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Mailing 2, Feb 23, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Whirlpool Decision, Feb 27, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Metzenbaum Letter, Feb 29, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, Feb 29, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Congress Watch/Big Business Day (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Mailing 3, Feb - Apr 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Signers of Ad "Danger-Nuclear War", Mar 2, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Call for Hearings, Congressional Record, Mar 5, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Social Democratcs, USA, Mar 7, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - To Stuart Matt, Mar 9, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Moynihan to Rubin, Mar 10, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Guild Address List (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Ed Cross to Moynihan and to Javits, Mar 14, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Urban Environment Conference Mailing, Mar 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - OSHA Oversight Hearings: Williams Opening Statement, Mar 18, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Testimony Before the Committee on Human Labor & Resources, Mar 18-28, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Mark Nicas Letters, Mar 29, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Petitions (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Draft Letter to Senators for Local Union Members (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO Sub-Committee on Health and Standards Members List (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department Conference Notifications, Feb - Mar 1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Opposition Letters, Letters of Support for the Committee to Save OSHA, and Health Hazard Information, Feb 25, 1980 - Jun 2, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Senate/House Committee Lists (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Senate Committee on Labor and Human Relations Member List (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Letters to Congressmen Opposing S.2153, Mar 31, 1980 - Jun 12, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Congressional Responses to Opposition Letters, Feb 29, 1980 - May 23, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - New York Assembly Bill 7103-B on Hazardous Substances (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Information Requests, Apr 29, 1980 - May 27, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Letters from Congressmen and Senators to Committee to Save OSHA, Aug 28, 1980 - Sep 29, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Draft of Advertisement (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Union Responses, Positions, Jan 23, 1980 - Feb 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO 13th Convention's Position on Safety and Health, Nov 11-15, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council Statement Opposing S. 2153, Feb 23, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Environmental/Public Interst Resolutions, Jan 18, 1980 - Apr 14, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Environmentalists for Full Employment (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - National Lawyers Guild Resolution (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Newspaper Guild Resolution, Jan 30, 1980 - Feb 2, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - New York State AFL-CIO Resolutions, Jan 28, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Sierra Club Resolution, Feb 3, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - United Steelworkers of America Position, Feb 8, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - (Chicago?) Coalition of Occupational Safety and Health (CACOSH) (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Kanawha Valley Coalition on Occupational Safety and Health (KVCOSH), Jan 20, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Maryland Committee on Occupational Safety and Health (MaryCOSH), Feb 23, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - New York Committee on Occupational Safety and Health (NYCOSH), Feb 23, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Oneida-Herkimer Council on Occupational Safety and Health, Mar 18, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Philadelphia Area Project on Occupational Safety and Health (PhilaPOSH), Feb 1980 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Western New York Council on Occupational Safety and Health (WNYCOSH), Dec 1979 - Mar 1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation Forms (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation Form (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation Forms (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation Forms (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation Forms (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Confirmation of Participation Forms (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Committee to Save OSHA Individuals List for Mailing Names for NY Times Advertisement, May 23, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Liability Statements - Shufro, Goldsmith, Nagin, Love, Jun 12, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - New York Times Advertisement, Jun 15, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - New York Times, Dec 20, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Wall Street Journal, Dec 20, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Metal Working News, Dec 31, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Star-Ledger, Dec 28, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - UAW Washington Report, Dec 21, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Californial AFL-CIO News, Jan 1980 - Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - UE News, Jan 21, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO News-Department of Public Relations-Labor News Conference, Jan 20, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Galesburg Labor News, Jan 30 & 31, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Labor Unity, Jan & Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - MESA Educator, Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Occupational Hazards, Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Steelabor, Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO News, Feb 2, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Northern California Labor, Feb 8, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - US News and World Report, Feb 11, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - In These Times, Feb 12, 1980 - Feb 19, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Galesburg Labor News, Feb 21, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - AFL-CIO News, Feb 23, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - GWA News, Feb 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Industrial Union Department AFL-CIO Newsletter, Jan - Apr 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, Mar 3, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Conservation Report, Mar 7, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - California AFL-CIO News, Mar 7, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - New York Times, Mar 17, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - STAND-UP, Spring 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Labor Union Legislative Alert (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - OCAW Health and Safety News (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - United Teachers (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Office and Professional Employees International Union White Collar (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Health and Safety Bulletin (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Shield (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Service Employees (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - AFL-CIO News (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union Record (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Bureau of National Affairs Current Report (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Washington Ethical Action Office Reports (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh Post Gazette (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Press Clips (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Solidarity Day 1981, Jul - Sep 1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - AFL-CIO Correspondence on OSHA, Feb 1981 - May 28, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - AFL-CIO Testimony on OSHA, Jul 1981 - Dec 1983 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Subseries B: NYCOSH (New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health) Conferences, 1980-1986
    - Occupational Disease Among Black Workers: An Annotated Bibliography by Morris Davis and Andrew Rowland, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - NYCOSH (New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health) Harlem Occupational Health Conference, Apr 23 - 25, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Harlem Occupational Health Conference, Apr 23 - 25, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Safety and Health Materials: Photocopiers (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Office Hazards Conference Planning Material, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Office Hazards Conference Packet, Nov 20, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Safety and Health Material: Office Hazards, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Is Your Job Killing You? Conference, Jun 1982 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - NYCOSH (New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health) VDT Conference, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Safety and Health Material: VDT, 1983-1986 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - VDT Conference (DC 37), Dec 8, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - VDT Regulations, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Mothering: "VDTs and Pregnancy", 1986 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Asbestos Conference Planning, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Asbestos Material, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - NYCOSH (New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health) Conference: Asbestos: Fighting a Killer, Nov 19, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - NYCOSH (New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health) Asbestos Task Force, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Asbestos Material, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Asbestos Material, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Subseries C: Health and Safety Activities and Information, 1981-1987
    - Department of Environmental Protection Draft Regulations for Asbestos Emmission Control, Jun / Jul 1986 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Environmental Protection Agency Asbestos Education Funds, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Linking the Professional with the Worker (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Department of Professional Employees, AFL-CIO Here Comes Tomorrow Conference (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Citizen Commission on Bhopal, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Bhopal Working Group, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Bhopal Working Group, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Asbestos Watch, Fall 1986 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - NYSUT Local List (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Workers' Compensation Material, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Workers' Compensation, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Main Street Legal: Workers' Compensation Reform, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Urban Environment Conference Inc./NYCOSH (New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health) Right to Know Conference, Nov 21, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Right to Know Material (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Richard Rice Case, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Public Citizen Health and Research Group and International Chemical Workers' Union Petition for an Emergency Standard for Cadium and Cadium Compounds, Jun 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Toxic Fire Safety Campaign (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Connecticut: Safety and Health Material (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - New Jersey: Right to Know and Workers' Compensation Material (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Proposed New York State Parental Leave Legislation (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - New York: Safety and Health Material (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Safety and Health Negotiating and Joint Management/Labor Committee Materials (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Grass Roots Organizing for the Environment (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cornell University: NYS School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Adjunct Faculty Federation (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Cornell University: NYS School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Right to Know Training, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Safety and Health Material: The Arts (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Safety and Health Material: Construction (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Safety and Health Material: Construction (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Safety and Health Material: Electrical (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Safety and Health Material: Firefighter (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Glass, Plastics, & Chemical Hazards Information (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Occupational Disease Material (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - General Safety and Health Material (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - United Food and Commercial Worker International Safety and Health Fact Sheets (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Bone Marrow Injury in Lithographers Exposed to Glycol Ethers and Organic Solvents Used in Multicolor Offset and Ultraviolet Curing Processes, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Ergonomic Aspects of Visual Display Terminals by E. Grandjean and E. Vigliani, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Whose Health and Welfare? The Press and Occupational Health by Chris Anne Raymond, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Hazardous Materials Emergency Planning Guide, Mar 1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Book Catalog (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Health PAC Health [Missing as of June 2011] (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Micro Waves News, Jan & Feb 1987 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Safety and Health Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - The Newspaper Guild Newspaper and Unit Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - New York Tunnel Workers News, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Worker Connection (UCLA), 1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters and Newspapers (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Labor Material (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Nine to Five National Organization of Working Women (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Union Rep Burnout (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Teaching Guide (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Series III: Unprocessed Material, 1971-2011
  The unprocessed materials in this collection relate to various health and safety campaigns. General information and research on these issues is also included. Major health and workers' issues documented include asbestos, needlestick injuries, workers' compensation, VDTs, and reproductive health. Professions represented in this series include teachers, transportation workers, government employees, health care employees, and others. NYCOSH's advocacy and general information on these issues are documented through correspondence, reports, fliers, pamphlets, posters, newsletters, government documents, news clippings, conference materials, financial records, and other materials.
  - Box 8, 1978-1988
    Local Newsletters and Leaflets re: Occupational Health, Booklets, Pamphlets, Handbooks, and Information Resources, Rules and Regulations, Safety Reports, Montifone Occupational Health: Why and How, Reports on Correspondence, Crime and Tunnel Syndrome, Coke Emission Regulations, Book Reviews, Sinai Medical Occupational History, Physicians and Workers' Compensation Files and Forms, Articles and Journals on Hazardous Materials, VDTs, Solvents, Food, NYCOSH Newspaper Clippings, Labor Songs and Graphics, NYCOSH (State, Local, National) Files, Fundraising Proposals and Meetings, Grants, Annual Report of Grant Support, Printing Bills and Workers Comp, Correspondence, Staff Reports, OSHA Files and Committees
  - Box 9, 1980-1987
    Occupational Health and Safety Reports and Pamphlets, Labor Education Center Correspondence, Memoranda and Assembly Bills, Bay Area COSH Fact Sheets, COSH Mailing Lists, Minority Workers: Reports, Newsletters, and Files, Childcare, Ceramics, Chemical Storage & Disposal Information, Journals & Reviews on Safety and Environment, Labor Safety and Health Institute Newsletters, Booklet: OSHA Standards, Construction and Safety Policy, U.S. Department of Health and Education Mailings, Brochures: Right to Know, U.S. Department of Labor News, Safety Newsletters, Educational Course Outline on Toxic Waste Disposal, Carpenters' Union Correspondence, Safety and Health Manuals, Report on New York State Safety and Health Concerns, Correspondence and Financial Records, Handouts
  - Box 10, 1986-1989
    NYCOSH: Fliers and Mailings on Criminal Prosecution for Occupational Injury, Death and Disease, Medical Bills, CT Interlocal Risk Management Agency, Local Correspondence and Mailings, Handwritten Notes and Suggestions, Reports, Bridge Market, Right to Know Letter, Correspondence and Newsletters: Jim Conti Material, Karen Cohen Files, Notes, Correspondence, and Reports, Angela DeVito files, Cate Poe Files, NY Staff Meeting Reports, Handwritten Notes on Transit Workers, TBTABA Mortality Study, SEIU Correspondence and Reports, Ruth Emler Recruitment, Westchester Meetings, NYCOSH Asbestos Meetings, Financial Records, Jackie Nowell's Files
  - Box 11, 1987-1992
    Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence: Jul 1 - Dec 31 1987, Local Files for Great Neck Teachers, Agenda and Handwritten Notes, Teacher Forms, Filers, and Information, Massanequa Federation of Teachers, AFT: Mattituck-Cutchogue T.A., Millbrook Training Files, Nassau Community College Staff Association and Locals, NYSUT Asbestos Abatement Reports, New Rochelle Training Materials, Correspondence, Pamphlets, Investigation Summaries, North Rockland Files, NYU, Oceanside School, Professional Staff Congress Training Materials, Rockville Center Teachers Association
  - Box 12, 1987-1994
    NYCOSH Board Agenda Correspondence, Membership Renewal Report, Accounts and Balance Sheets, Board Meeting Minutes, Workers' Compensation Committee, Proposed By-Law Amendment, Staff Meeting Agenda and Notes, Fashion Institute Training Manual, Files from Long Island Office, Mount Sinai Advisory Boards, Fliers, NYCOSH Resource Center, TB Reports, PERB Case concerning Tuberculosis Testing, NYS Department of Health Studies, TB in NYC Files, Correspondence, Reports, News, State Guidelines, Notes and Newsletters, NIOSH Recommended Guidelines, NIOSH-CDC-OSHA-GNYHA, OSHA Forms, Hep. C Files, Testing: Guidelines, Policy, Articles, Testimony and Hearings, Prevention and Reduction of Needlestick Injuries, National Leaders Conference on HIV/HBV, Federal Statistics
  - Box 13, 1974-1994
    NYCOSH Newsletters (and Correspondence regarding Newsletters): WOSH News, Work & Health, WashCOSH, WisCOSH, Hazards Communication, Bits of News (Mailings and Newspapers), B.C. Workers' Health Newsletter, TNCOSH Health & Safety, UticaCOSH, SACOSH, SCCOSH, RiCOSH, Rocky Mountain Project, SEACOSH, etc.
  - Box 14, 1974-1991
    Correspondence and Report to the Joint OER/PEF Health and Safety Committee, Draft Safety Petitions, Rules and Regulations, NYS/PEF Health and Safety Training Program (Monthly Report), Hunter College Materials, New York State Employee's Health and Safety Report, Booklets and Information on National OSH, VDT Legislation and NYS Campaign Material, Exclusive Sheet Brochure & Articles, Resources, Translations and Forms, NYCOSH Reports, VDT Newsletters and Presentations, Meetings Overview and Minutes, Health and Safety Training Guidelines, Training Correspondence, OCAW Health and Safety News, Lab Safety and Hazard Recognition Brochures, Pamphlets, and Newsletters, International Chemical Workers Union, Institute for Labor Studies Files, Fact Sheets + Requests, HMO Packets, Memoranda, Fax, and Handwritten Notes
  - Box 15, 1987-1992
    NYCOSH Union Membership Forms, Benefits and Claims, International Board of Teamsters, Locals Correspondence, Payroll and Balance Sheets, Newspapers, TWU Information and Memoranda, Asbestos and Room Air Quality Tests, Air Transport Files, Handwritten Notes, Balances, News, United Food and Commercial Workers, Joint Board Union Newsletters, Health Conference Fliers, WGA Files, Con Edison Sites Visits and Reports, Schematics, Handwritten Notes, Outlines, Power Plant Reports, UFT Grant Surveys, United Federation of Teachers Contract, Newsletter on OSHA Guidelines, Central Islip Teachers Association Files
  - Box 16, 1971-1993
    NYCOSH Potential Health Hazard Notices and Materials, Occupational Safety and Health Brochures, Health and Safety News, BHOPAL Files, Hazard Elimination Through Local Participation Act, Right to Know Files, Draft Summaries, OSHA Personnel Guides and Record Keeping, OSHA Articles, OSHA under Reagan: Notices, Files, News, Hazard Reports, Balance Sheets and Reports, Talking Points on Worker Safety and Health, Newspaper Supplements, Safety and Health Brochures, New Jersey Environmental Federation, NCCOSH, NHCOSH, Medical Monitoring News, NYS Board of Standards and Appeals, OSHA Newsletters, COSH Addresses, Injured Workers of New York Correspondence and Reports, American Labor Newsletter, Solidarity Magazine, Newspaper Clippings, State-by-State COSH Organizations, JOSHRC Newsletter
  - Box 17, 1980-1995
    CWA Negotiations: General Co. of California, Correspondence to and from NYCOSH, Newspaper Articles, Occupational Health Newsletter, Waste and Superfund Programs, State Bulletins and Newsletters on Occupational Health, Alice Hamilton Quarterly, State COSH Fliers, News, and Leaflets, Correspondence from COSH AFL-CIO Affiliates
  - Box 18, 1980-1989
    Various State VDT Legislation and Guidelines, Executive Orders, International (Trade Union) Guidelines, VDT Coalition Meetings, Agendas, Minutes, NYC VDT Bill: May 19 Testimony, Asbestos Handling Course Material, EPA Reports, Paper Workers Material, GMB Safety Reps Handbook, Safety Reps Guide and Handbook, Organizing and Union Materials and Regulations, CWA -- Occupational Safety and Health Fact Sheets, Conference Materials, Brochures, Handwritten Notes, Asbestos Control Program: Rules and Regulation
  - Box 19, 1982-1988
    NYCOSH Incoming and Outgoing Correspondence: Jul 1984-1986, Staff Issues, Mailings, Memoranda, Reports, Forms, Environmental Cancer Information, Contributions and Congressional Awards, Steering Committee (Mailing List & Sheet with Addresses & Phone Numbers), Financial Records
  - Box 20, 1982-1992